Legislative Correspondents Association of New York State; Records apap357
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
The Legislative Correspondents' Association of the State of New York Records
1892-2024
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap357
11.44 cubic ft.
24 U-matic tape.
8 Reels
This collection contains materials about The Legislative Correspondents' Association of the State of New York, especially its celebrated annual dinner held since 1900.
Folder 1
Access
Access to this collection is primarily unrestricted. There is one restricted box of two autographed show programs within the second series, access can be provided upon request.
Acquisition Information
Current and former members of The Legislative Correspondents Association of New York State Susan Arbetter, Kyle Hughes, and Ron Kermani donated the materials in this collection to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives in 2015-2016. Kyle Hughes donated additional materials in 2019 and 2022. The 2022 accession contained the LCA show files of longtime stage manager Jill Coloney. In 2024, Miranda Spivack donated a small number of files from her late father, Robert Spivack, who was past president of the organization and Michael Carrese, a former member of the organization, also donated a small amount of material.
Historical Note
The Legislative Correspondents' Association of the State of New York (LCA), which began in 1890, is composed of journalists covering the State Capitol in Albany. It is said to be one of the oldest organizations of newspapermen in the country. It was not until 1965 that women were permitted to join the LCA, although they were correspondents at the capital at the time. This Collection reflects the organization as a whole rather than specific reporters, with the exception of those referenced in the subject files.
The LCA holds a dinner and satirical show each year, since the inaugural one given for Governor Theodore Roosevelt in 1900, poking fun at New York politics and politicians. The program has grown from the simple beginnings of dinner and hijinks to the elaborate show put on for several hundred state politicians and guests that we have today. The proceeds from the show go to help local charities throughout New York State.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes administrative and financial records, correspondence, photographs, slides, and member files from The Legislative Correspondents' Association of the State of New York (LCA). The majority of the collection, however, consists of materials from the LCA's annual dinner and show, including programs, invitations, tickets, seating charts, scripts and actor's materials, video, audio, film, and songs.
Please note that not all dates are inclusive.
Arrangement of the Collection
The materials are arranged chronologically within each of the three series.
Legislative reporting--New York (State); Journalists--New York (State); Correspondence; Photographs; Souvenir programs; Admission tickets; Albany, New York; Politics and Politicians; Legislative Correspondents' Association of the State of New York
- Administrative, 1892-2007; 2.65 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  The Administrative series consists of Board and business meeting minutes, constitutions, proposed changes to the constitution, annual and executive meeting files, files of some Club Presidents, some show planning, finances, and budgets. It houses some of the earliest records about the organization. This series also contains information about membership, but not in depth information on specific reporters.
  - Reporters of New York State Senate and Assembly, 1892-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photocopies of Meeting Minutes and Membership, 1898-1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Copies of Articles Pertaining to LCA History, 1900; 1903; 1905 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Membership Lists, 1900-1921 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes and Membership, 1900-1925 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Membership Card File and Publishers Represented at State Capital, 1900-1986 (Card-file 1)
  - Constitution of the LCA, 1909; 1925-1926; 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Show Information, 1913-1927 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Minutes and Membership, 1915-1916; 1918; 1936; 1952-1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Correspondence, 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Membership, Correspondence, and Notes, 1919-1928; 1935-1938; 1950-1954; 1962-1965; 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Minutes and Membership, 1926-1939; 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Black and White Photos of Unidentified Headshots, Probably Members and Robert Spoor, 1930; 1963; 1973; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Meeting Minutes and Membership, 1935-1939 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Expenditures, Bank Balance, and Show Committee, 1935; 1948; 1951-1952; 1955; 1964-1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Official List LCA NYS Legislature, 1944; 1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Account Ledger, 1944-1970 (Oversized 1)
  - Correspondence and Article Regarding Robert Spivak Election as LCA President, 1948-1949; Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, Correspondence, and Show Information, 1948-1955 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - List of Officers and Board of Directors, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Meeting Minutes and Membership, 1951-1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Group Photos, Probably Members, 1957; 1960-1962; 1966; 1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, Correspondence, and Show, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Albany News Bureau Expense Analysis, 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Membership Lists, 1958; 1960-1961; 1963-1970; 1972 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Show Information, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Show Information, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Invitations and Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Show Information, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Membership Lists and Cast Party Announcements, 1961; 1963-1965; 1967; 1971 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Correspondence, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, Invitations, and Show Information, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Correspondence, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Correspondence, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - News Reporters Assigned to New York State Legislature, 1966-1968; 1970-1975; 1980; 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Correspondence, 1966-1969; 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Membership Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Membership and Correspondence, 1969-1970; 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, Invitations, and Show Information, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Edward Bates' Death, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Minutes, Membership, and Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Meeting Minutes and Membership, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Minutes and Membership, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Phone Calls and Usage, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Invoices and Financial Information, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Minutes and Resolutions, 1974-1977; 1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Invoices for Telephone Calls and Typewriter Rentals, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Tax Information and Dues Receipts, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Wake For Long Island Press Photograph, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Luncheon, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Legal Documents Dealing With Tax Exempt Status and Letters of Incorporation, 1978; 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Financial Documents, 1981; 1985; 1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Misc. Articles and Letters, 1982-1983; Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Inner Circle Inc. Charitable Donations Financial Reports, 1982-1984; 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Copy of Speech about President and Press by Harold Brayman to Walter J. Mordaunt, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Christmas and Cocktail Party Invoices and Correspondence, 1985-1987; 1990; Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Invoices for Newspapers, 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Members' Obituaries, 1985; 1989; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Attorney Documents, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes and Correspondence with Andrew O'Rourke, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Invoices From Attorneys and Accountants, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence and Documents, 1987-1988; 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Unbound Ledgers, 1987-1989 (Flat-file 1)
  - Federal and State Income Tax Returns, 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Financials, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Tax Exempt Status Paperwork, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Certificate of Incorporation and IRS Letters and Documents, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Tax Exempt Information, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Membership, Finances, and Legal, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Invoices and Correspondence with IRS and NYS Taxes, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Account Ledger, 1989-1990 (Oversized 1)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Invoices, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Building Passes, 1990; 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Addresses For News Reporters Cards, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bills and Tax Prep, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Department Office of General Services Billing for Parking, 1993; 1995 (Flat-file 2)
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Letterhead and Envelope, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Notes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Membership Index Card File, Undated (Card-file 1)
  - Officers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Troy Newspapers and Correspondents, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
- LCA Show, 1902-2024; 7.89 cubic ft.
  This series contains information specific to the LCA's annual show. The files contain information about a specific year's show including: finances, invoices, programs, scripts, invitations, correspondence, committees, attendees, menus, videos, photographs, and slides. The 2024 accession has granted almost all of the show programs in the Association's history. This series contains the bulk of the collection starting with the earliest show program dated 1902.
  Some early show information may also be found in the administration series, where it was comingled with executive and membership materials.
  - Show Program, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photocopy of 1904 Program (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photos from Binder labeled "30s and 40s" (1 of 2), 1904; 1908; 1912; 1930-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photos from Binder labeled "30s and 40s" (2 of 2), 1904; 1908; 1912; 1930-1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    General
    This item contains derogatory and potentially harmful depictions of minority communities. These representations reflect the prejudices and biases of the time in which they were created and may be offensive or distressing. We present this material as part of the historical record, not as an endorsement of the views it contains.
  - Show Programs, 1907; 1909-1912 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Photocopy of 1908 Show Program (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "The Big Stick and the Golf Stick" Book, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Show Program, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Show Programs, 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Show Songs, 1914-2007 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Show Programs, 1916; 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Show Program, 1917 (Oversized 3)
  - Show Programs, 1920; 1922-1924 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Guests and Table Directory, 1925-1957 (Flat-file 3)
  - Show Programs, 1925-1929 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Show Program Cover and Photos, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Show Program and Photos, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Show Programs, 1930-1937 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Show Program and Photos, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Show Programs, 1940-1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Program Covers and Identified Photos (1 of 2), 1941-1946; 1948-1949; 1952-1965; 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Program Covers and Identified Photos (2 of 2), 1941-1946; 1948-1949; 1952-1965; 1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Diagram of the 1944 State Chamber (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Guests of 1944 Show (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Show Programs, 1945-1949 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Article about LCA Show, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Guest List and Invite to Attorney General Wendell P. Brown, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Show Programs, 1950-1954 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Show Finances and Correspondence, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Show Programs, 1955-1959 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Show Correspondence, Menu, and Attendees, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Show Script, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Show Menu, Invoices, Invites, Committees, and Escort Assignments, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Show Invitations and Invite Lists, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Show Photos, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Photos and Articles, 1959; 1962; Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Show Finances and Correspondence, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Show Programs, 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Guests and Table Directory, 1960-1971; 1973; 1975-1979 (Flat-file 4)
  - Show Correspondence, Menus, and Finance, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Show Photos and Accompanying Letter, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Show Finances, Correspondence, Attendees, Photo, and Guests List, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Show Finances, Correspondence, Menus, and Invoices, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Show Reel-to-Reel, 1964 (Reel 1)
  - Show Finances and Correspondence, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Show Reel-to-Reel (1 of 2), 1965 (Reel 2)
  - Show Reel-to-Reel (2 of 2), 1965 (Reel 3)
  - Show Finances, Correspondence, and Program Cover, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Show Finance, Correspondence, Schedule, and Program Cover, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Show Photos of Members' Wives, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Show Programs, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Show Finances and Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Program Covers and Identified Show Photos (1 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Program Covers and Identified Show Photos (2 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Show Finance and Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - LCA Vinyl Songs of 1968 with Lyric Sheets 33 1/3 Microgroove (Oversized 3)
  - Show Photos and Program Cover, 1968; Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Show Finances and Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Show Program Cover and Photos, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Show Finances, Correspondence, and Program Cover, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Show Programs, 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Show Finances, Correspondence, and Schedule, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Show Program and Photos, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Show Finances, Correspondence, and Script, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Show Invitation, Ticket, Finances, Correspondence, Script, Photos, and Program Cover, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Show Finances, Invoices, and Correspondence, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Show Invoices, Show Schedule, and Correspondence, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Show Finances and Invoices, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Show Costs and Ticket Sales, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Show Reel-to-Reel (1 of 2), 1976 (Reel 4)
  - Show Reel-to-Reel (2 of 2), 1976 (Reel 5)
  - Show Invoices, Committees, and Correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Show Photo Album, 1977 (Oversized 2)
  - Charitable Donations From Show, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Show Finances and Correspondence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Show Finances, Correspondence, and Schedule, 1979; Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Show Correspondence, Attendees, and Invoices, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Guests and Table Directory, 1980-2014 (Flat-file 5)
  - Show Programs, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Backstage Show Slides, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Show Correspondence and Cast List, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Show Slides, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Show Video (1 of 2), 1981 (Umatic 1)
  - Show Video (2 of 2), 1981 (Umatic 2)
  - Show Invoices, Cast List, and Script, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Showbook, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Show Invoices, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Show Costs, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Show Photos Act 1, 1 Act 1, 2+4 Act 1, 3 Act 2, 1 and Act 2, 2, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Show Video (1 of 2), 1983 (Umatic 3)
  - Show Video (2 of 2), 1983 (Umatic 4)
  - Show Photos A-E, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Show Photos F-I, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Show Video (1 of 2), 1984 (Umatic 5)
  - Show Video (2 of 2), 1984 (Umatic 6)
  - Show Cassette (1 of 2), 1985 (Cassette 1)
  - Show Cassette (2 of 2), 1985 (Cassette 2)
  - Show Script, Cast, Invoices, and Insurance, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Show Video (1 of 2), 1985 (Umatic 7)
  - Show Video (2 of 2), 1985 (Umatic 8)
  - Charitable Donations From Show, 1985-1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Show Finances and Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Show Video (1 of 2), 1986 (Umatic 9)
  - Show Video (2 of 2), 1986 (Umatic 10)
  - Show Invoices, Correspondence, Invites, Ticket Sales, Script, and Speech, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Show Video (1 of 2), 1987 (Umatic 11)
  - Show Video (2 of 2), 1987 (Umatic 12)
  - Show Video, 1987 (Vhs 1)
  - Working Event Binder, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Show T-Shirts, 1987-1988; 1999-2000; 2002 (Oversized 1)
  - Show Film, 1988 (Film 1)
  - Show Photos Unidentified, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Show Scripts and Actor's "Bible", Finances, Script, Correspondence, and Article, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Show Video, 1988 (Vhs 2)
  - Show Video (1 of 2), 1988 (Umatic 13)
  - Show Video (2 of 2), 1988 (Umatic 14)
  - Tickets Sold, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Show Film, 1989 (Film 2)
  - Show Invoices, Invite, and Script, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Show Video, 1989 (Umatic 15)
  - Show Invoices, Invite, and Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Show Film, 1990 (Film 3)
  - Show Video, 1990 (Umatic 16)
  - Show Video, 1990 (Vhs 3)
  - Show Invitation Lists, 1990-1993; 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Show Programs, 1990-1999 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Show Invoices, Script, and Actor's "Bible", 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Show Video, 1991 (Vhs 4)
  - Show Film, 1992 (Film 4)
  - Show Finances, Correspondence, Invite, and Script, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Show VHS, 1992 (Vhs 5)
  - Show Invoices, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Show Video (1 of 2), 1993 (Umatic 17)
  - Show Video (2 of 2), 1993 (Umatic 18)
  - Show Video, 1993 (Vhs 6)
  - LCA Program Design Transparencies, 1993-1996; 1998; 1999; Undated (Oversized 3)
  - Show Attendees and Seating, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Show Video, 1994 (Umatic 19)
  - Show Video, 1994 (Vhs 7)
  - Show Correspondence, Invite, Table Seating, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Show Video, 1995 (Vhs 8)
  - Show Video, 1996 (Beta 1)
  - Show Invites, Photos, Seating, Finances, and Actor's "Bible", 1996 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Show Video, 1996 (Vhs 9)
  - Show Video, 1997 (Beta 2)
  - Show Invites, Show Script, and Photos, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Show Video, 1997 (Vhs 10)
  - Show Video, 1998 (Beta 3)
  - Show Photos, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible", Finances, Invite, Article, and Correspondence, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Show Video, 1998 (Umatic 20)
  - Show Video, 1998 (Umatic 21)
  - Show Video, 1998 (Vhs 11)
  - Show Video, 1999 (Beta 4)
  - Show Photos, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Show Photos, 1999 (Vhs 12)
  - Show Script, Invites, and Articles, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Show Scripts and Actor's "Bible", 1999 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Show Video, 1999 (Umatic 22)
  - Show Photos Backstage Identified and Unidentified, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Show Photos of Table Seating, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Show Video, 2000 (Vhs 13)
  - Show Script, Article, Finances, Invites, and Correspondence, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Show Scripts and Actor's "Bible", 2000 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Signed Hillary Clinton Show Program - [RESTRICTED], 2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Please speak with an archivist to view this material.
  - Show Programs, 2000-2009 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Show Digital Video, 2001 (Dvcam 1)
  - Show Invite, Script, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Show Photos Backstage (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Show Photos Backstage (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Show Scripts and Actor's "Bible", 2001 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Show Video, 2001 (Vhs 14)
  - Invite, Finances, and Correspondence, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Show Photos, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Show Scripts and Actor's "Bible", 2002 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Show Video, 2002 (Vhs 15)
  - Submissions For Annual LCA Writing Award, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Actor's "Bible", 2003 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NY 1 News Report on LCA Show, 2003 (Vhs 16)
  - Show Dinner Photos, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Show Digital Video, 2003 (Dvcam 2)
  - Show Photos, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible", Invite, Finances, and Correspondence, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Show Video, 2003 (Vhs 17)
  - Show Digital Video, 2004 (Dvcam 3)
  - Show Photos, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible", Invite, Finances, and Correspondence, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Show Video, 2004 (Vhs 18)
  - Show Digital Video, 2005 (Dvcam 4)
  - Show DVD, 2005 (Dvd 1)
  - Show Photos, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Show Scripts and Actor's "Bible", Invite, and Article, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Show Video, 2005 (Vhs 19)
  - Show Digital Video, 2006 (Dvcam 5)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible", and Invites, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Show Video, 2006 (Vhs 20)
  - Show Digital Video, 2007 (Dvcam 6)
  - Show Photos, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Show Script, Actor's "Bible" and Invites, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Show Digital Video, 2008 (Dvcam 7)
  - Show Script, Actor's "Bible" and Invites, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Show Photos, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible" and Invite, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible" and Invite, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Show Programs, 2010-2019 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Show Digital Video, 2011 (Dvcam 8)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible" and Invite, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible" and Invite, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Program Inventory, 2012; 2014 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible", 2013 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Show Script and Guest List, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible", 2014 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Show Script, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Signed Andrew Cuomo Show Program - [RESTRICTED], 2014 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Show Scripts and Actor's "Bible", 2015 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Show Script and Seating Chart, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Show Script, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible", 2016 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible", 2017 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible", 2018 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Show Script and Actor's "Bible", 2019 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Show Programs, 2022-2023 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Final Script, 2023 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - LCA Show Digital Video, 2024 May 22
  - First Act of Show, Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Possible Television Coverage of Show Budget Pie, Undated (Umatic 22)
  - Possible Television Coverage of Show HalleJulia Chorus at Head, Undated (Umatic 23)